{
    "id": "7087ad402a48485daf4366a717613cba",
    "title": "Confusing Pairs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "…………………. knowledge is a dangerous thing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "A little",
                "Little"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a32544dfdfb947a694150b9e3936de0e"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. children are innocent.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Little",
                "A little"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ad99d3af70314dad97887e276a7c2ac5"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. children are interested in reading.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Few",
                "A few"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "42aa59e0c4764bd2b2ec9c3c2ba258f9"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has ………………….. buildings of his own.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "63490ee767034ed287a42a7f33262934"
        },
        {
            "question": "The …………………. half of the film is more interesting than the former.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "later",
                "latter"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4702da6157a24a16a5aa10c6af6dc9c1"
        },
        {
            "question": "My …………………. brother works abroad.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "elder",
                "older",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e67fa0de8bfd4438910fa8424e379852"
        },
        {
            "question": "Trains run ……………….. five minutes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "every",
                "each"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "657cf20f2dcd43a2a8c5d84b2c97a9d8"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… bag is this?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Whose",
                "Who's"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2d48ca1fa47f43f1addafcdf90c825bd"
        },
        {
            "question": "The dog has had ………………….. breakfast.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "its",
                "it's"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1c54a6b6fdac4be0a42e1478e55c50c0"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… is something wrong with this computer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "There",
                "Their",
                "There's"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "47d2006c1e7e4a54a21d153e6a19d3c2"
        }
    ]
}